Guide to The Women's Sports Foundation Records 1950-2019 (bulk, 1974-2018) MS 3199
New-York Historical Society
- Series IV. Departmental records, 1971-2018; 146 Linear feet in 146 record cartons
  - Subseries IV.E. Events and development records, 1976-2018; 39 Linear feet in 39 record cartons
    - NGWSD, 1998 (Offsite-box 155, Folder 24)
    - Salute to Women in Sports (1 of 3 folders), 1998 (Offsite-box 155, Folder 25)
    - Salute to Women in Sports (2 of 3 folders), 1998 (Offsite-box 156, Folder 1-2)
    - NGWSD (2 folders), 1999 (Offsite-box 156, Folder 3-4)
    - Spirit of Sports Awards, 1999 (Offsite-box 156, Folder 5)
    - Annual summit, 1999 (Offsite-box 156, Folder 6)
    - Annual Salute to Women in Sports, 1999 (Offsite-box 156, Folder 7)
    - Summit, 2000 (Offsite-box 156, Folder 8)
    - Aim Higher, 2000 (Offsite-box 156, Folder 9)
    - Annual Salute to Women in Sports (5 folders), 2000-2004 (Offsite-box 156, Folder 10-14)
    - Sneaker Day, 2003 (Offsite-box 156, Folder 15)
    - Basketball classic, 1999 (Offsite-box 156, Folder 16)
    - Summit (6 folders), 1999 (Offsite-box 156, Folder 17-22)
    - Summit (5 folders), 2000 (Offsite-box 156, Folder 23-27)
    - NYAD (5 of 15 folders), 1998 (Offsite-box 156, Folder 28-32)
    - NYAD (10 of 15 folders), 1998 (Offsite-box 157, Folder 1-10)
    - NYAD (16 folders), 1999 (Offsite-box 157, Folder 11-26)
    - Planet Hollywood, 2000 (Offsite-box 157, Folder 27)
    - NYAD (8 folders), 2000 (Offsite-box 157, Folder 28-35)
    - NGWSD (7 folders), 1999 (Offsite-box 157, Folder 36-42)
    - NGWSD (6 folders), 2000 (Offsite-box 157, Folder 43-48)
    - NGWSD (5 folders), 2001 (Offsite-box 158, Folder 1-5)
    - Summit poster contest (3 folders), 2000 (Offsite-box 158, Folder 6-8)
    - Summit poster contest grades K-1 [disassembled binder], 2000 (Offsite-box 158, Folder 9)
    - Summit poster contest grades 2-3 [disassembled binder], 2000 (Offsite-box 158, Folder 10)
    - Summit poster contest grades 4-6 [disassembled binder] (2 folders), 2000 (Offsite-box 158, Folder 11-12)
    - Summit poster contest grades 5-7 [disassembled binder], 2000 (Offsite-box 158, Folder 13)
    - Summit playbook (4 of 12 folders), 2001 (Offsite-box 158, Folder 14-17)
    - Summit playbook (8 of 12 folders), 2001 (Offsite-box 159, Folder 1-8)
    - NYAD clinics (3 folders), 2001 (Offsite-box 159, Folder 9-11)
    - NYAD (3 of 11 folders), 2001 (Offsite-box 159, Folder 12-14)
    - NYAD (8 of 11 folders), 2001 (Offsite-box 160, Folder 1-8)
    - NGWSD (5 folders), 2002 (Offsite-box 160, Folder 9-13)
    - NYAD (11 folders), 2002 (Offsite-box 161, Folder 1-11)
    - NGWSD, 1994 (Offsite-box 161, Folder 12)
    - NGWSD planning, 1999 (Offsite-box 161, Folder 13)
    - NGWSD planning (2 folders), 2000 (Offsite-box 162, Folder 1-2)
    - Annual Salute to Women in Sports programs (3 folders), 1997-2003 (Offsite-box 162, Folder 3-5)
    - Annual Summit (2 folders), 2000 (Offsite-box 162, Folder 6-7)
    - NYAD, 2000 (Offsite-box 162, Folder 8)
    - Summit, 1996-2001 (Offsite-box 162, Folder 9)
    - NYAD invitations, 1998-2007 (Offsite-box 162, Folder 10)
    - Billies invitations, 2006-2008 (Offsite-box 162, Folder 11)
    - Invitations, 1998-2001 (Offsite-box 162, Folder 12)
    - NYAD programs (2 folders), 2004-2006 (Offsite-box 162, Folder 13-14)
    - Billies programs, 2006-2007 (Offsite-box 162, Folder 15)
    - NGWSD, 1996-2009 (Offsite-box 162, Folder 16)
    - Membership/ fundraising, 2005-2008 (Offsite-box 162, Folder 17)
    - Annual Salute to Women in Sports [disassembled binder] (2 folders), 2007 (Offsite-box 162, Folder 18-19)
    - Living Modules playbook [disassembled binder], 2006 (Offsite-box 163, Folder 1)
    - Billie Awards [disassembled binder], 2007 (Offsite-box 163, Folder 2)
    - The Billies playbook [disassembled binder], 2008 (Offsite-box 163, Folder 3)
    - Marathons playbook [disassembled binder] (2 folders), 2008 (Offsite-box 163, Folder 4-5)
    - Membership mailing, 2002 (Offsite-box 163, Folder 6)
    - Development correspondence, 2004 (Offsite-box 163, Folder 7)
    - Survey and donation forms, 2001 (Offsite-box 163, Folder 8)
    - Membership and donation forms (3 folders), 2003 (Offsite-box 163, Folder 9-11)
    - NYAD corporate receipts and donations (13 of 53 folders), 1984-1987 (Offsite-box 164, Folder 10-22)
    - NYAD corporate receipts and donations (22 of 53 folders), 1984-1987 (Offsite-box 165, Folder 1-22)
    - NYAD corporate receipts and donations (18 of 53 folders), 1984-1987 (Offsite-box 166, Folder 1-18)
    - NYAD follow up thank you letters, 1990 (Offsite-box 166, Folder 19)
    - New York Dinner, 1987 (Offsite-box 166, Folder 20)
    - Car service and chauffeurs receipts from NYAD, 1991 (Offsite-box 166, Folder 21)
    - NYAD (3 folders), 1991 (Offsite-box 166, Folder 22-24)
    - NYAD (8 folders), 1990 (Offsite-box 166, Folder 25-32)
    - Sporting Match Ford, 1991 (Offsite-box 166, Folder 33)
    - Sporting Match, 1990 (Offsite-box 166, Folder 34)
    - Dinner program, 1991 (Offsite-box 166, Folder 35)
    - Evening, 1991 (Offsite-box 166, Folder 36)
    - Salute to Women in Sports, 1991 (Offsite-box 166, Folder 37)
    - NY dinner VNR, 1991 (Offsite-box 166, Folder 38)
    - NY dinner media, 1991 (Offsite-box 166, Folder 39)
    - Press conference, circa 1991 (Offsite-box 167, Folder 1)
    - Sudafed Awards dinner press releases (2 folders), circa 1990-1991 (Offsite-box 167, Folder 2-3)
    - Corporates and individuals attending awards dinners (S.F.) [disassembled binder], 1980-1986 (Offsite-box 167, Folder 4)
    - [Contact information], 2001 (Offsite-box 167, Folder 5)
    - New events, 2001 (Offsite-box 167, Folder 6)
    - Family circle, 2001 (Offsite-box 167, Folder 7)
    - Summit, 2003 (Offsite-box 167, Folder 8)
    - Development, 2001 (Offsite-box 167, Folder 9)
    - Events database, 1998-2001 (Offsite-box 167, Folder 10)
    - Judo clinic, 1998 (Offsite-box 167, Folder 11)
    - Summit hotel, 2001 (Offsite-box 167, Folder 12)
    - Aim Higher, 2001 (Offsite-box 167, Folder 13)
    - Summit, 2000 (Offsite-box 167, Folder 14)
    - Summit Washington, DC, 1999 (Offsite-box 167, Folder 15)
    - Summit hotel, 1998 (Offsite-box 167, Folder 16)
    - NYAD, 1999 (Offsite-box 167, Folder 17)
    - NYAD final table seating and money report, 1998 (Offsite-box 167, Folder 18)
    - NGWSD, 2000 (Offsite-box 167, Folder 19)
    - NGWSD, 1999 (Offsite-box 167, Folder 20)
    - NGWSD (2 folders), 1998 (Offsite-box 167, Folder 21-22)
    - Summit staff/ travel/ transport, 2001 (Offsite-box 167, Folder 23)
    - LOC Summit, 2001 (Offsite-box 167, Folder 24)
    - Aim Higher, 2001 July 19 (Offsite-box 167, Folder 25)
    - White House project, 2001 (Offsite-box 167, Folder 26)
    - Chase championships (Offsite-box 167, Folder 27)
    - WBCA (Women's Basketball Coaches Association), St. Louis, 2001 (Offsite-box 167, Folder 28)
    - AAHPERD (American Alliance for Health, Physical Education, Recreation and Dance), 2001 (Offsite-box 167, Folder 29)
    - WBCA (Women's Basketball Coaches Association), 1998 (Offsite-box 167, Folder 30)
    - [Outreach notes], 1998-2001 (Offsite-box 167, Folder 31)
    - Project outreach, 1998 (Offsite-box 167, Folder 32)
    - AVCA (American Volleyball Coaches Association), 2000 (Offsite-box 167, Folder 33)
    - Museum fundraiser Dallas, TX (2 folders), 2001 June 15-17 (Offsite-box 167, Folder 34-35)
    - NYAD, 2000 (Offsite-box 167, Folder 36)
    - NYAD (14 folders), 2001 (Offsite-box 168, Folder 1-14)
    - NGWSD (17 folders), 1993 (Offsite-box 168, Folder 15-31)
    - WNBA game night, 2000 (Offsite-box 168, Folder 32)
    - Detroit Shock event, 1999 (Offsite-box 168, Folder 33)
    - Judy Street FL event, 2003 February (Offsite-box 168, Folder 34)
    - NGWSD DC event, 2003 February 3 (Offsite-box 168, Folder 35)
    - Hull California event, 2003 (Offsite-box 168, Folder 36)
    - Sneaker Day, 2003 (Offsite-box 168, Folder 37)
    - Muscatine event (2 folders), 2002 (Offsite-box 168, Folder 38-39)
    - NGWSD, 2002 (Offsite-box 168, Folder 40)
    - Jeanette Lee/ Colorado event database work, 2002 (Offsite-box 168, Folder 41)
    - Maddy event, 2002 (Offsite-box 169, Folder 1)
    - NYAD (3 folders), 2001 (Offsite-box 169, Folder 2-4)
    - Washington DC events, 2002 (Offsite-box 169, Folder 5)
    - c200 event (2 folders), 2001 May 30 (Offsite-box 169, Folder 6-7)
    - Texas museum event, 2001 June 16 (Offsite-box 169, Folder 8)
    - Dallas Texas event, 2000 November 21 (Offsite-box 169, Folder 9)
    - Harvard MBA event, 2001 January (Offsite-box 169, Folder 10)
    - Bagley DC event, 2001 June 20 (Offsite-box 169, Folder 11)
    - WUSA inaugural game DC event, 2001 April 14 (Offsite-box 169, Folder 12)
    - Aim Higher, 2000 (Offsite-box 169, Folder 13)
    - Chase NYC women's tennis hosting, 2000 November (Offsite-box 169, Folder 14)
    - Cedar Crest cocktail reception, 2000 (Offsite-box 169, Folder 15)
    - NYAD (3 folders), 2000 (Offsite-box 169, Folder 16-18)
    - Summit, 2000 (Offsite-box 169, Folder 19)
    - Summit, 1999 (Offsite-box 169, Folder 20)
    - NYAD (3 folders), 1999 (Offsite-box 169, Folder 21-23)
    - Martina event (7 folders), 1998 (Offsite-box 169, Folder 24-30)
    - NYAD table lists, 1995-1997 (Offsite-box 169, Folder 31)
    - NYAD script/ PR, 1998 (Offsite-box 169, Folder 32)
    - Jennifer Leeds bike ride, 1997 (Offsite-box 169, Folder 33)
    - Muscatine event, 2002 (Offsite-box 170, Folder 1)
    - Sudafed Women's Sports Awards Dinner programs and invitations (4 folders), 1992 October 5 (Offsite-box 170, Folder 2-5)
    - Touring exhibit (2 folders), 1996-1997 (Offsite-box 170, Folder 6-7)
    - FANS first enterprises, 1996-1997 (Offsite-box 170, Folder 8)
    - Mall tour, 1999 (Offsite-box 170, Folder 9)
    - CIBC (2 folders), 1997-1999 (Offsite-box 170, Folder 10-11)
    - NYAD, 2000 (Offsite-box 170, Folder 12)
    - Sponsors, 1999 (Offsite-box 170, Folder 13)
    - Golf outing, 1998 (Offsite-box 170, Folder 14)
    - NGWSD, 1994 (Offsite-box 170, Folder 15)
    - Events company, 1999 (Offsite-box 170, Folder 16)
    - Chase event, 1999 (Offsite-box 170, Folder 17)
    - Waldorf-Astoria, 1997-1999 (Offsite-box 170, Folder 18)
    - Logos, 1999 (Offsite-box 170, Folder 19)
    - Salute to Women in Sports invitations, 1995 (Offsite-box 170, Folder 20)
    - Sprit of Sport (3 folders), 1999 (Offsite-box 170, Folder 21-23)
    - WSF membership (Offsite-box 171, Folder 1)
    - Spirit of Sports Awards (3 folders), 1999 (Offsite-box 171, Folder 2-4)
    - Title IX, 1996 (Offsite-box 171, Folder 5)
    - Summit (2 folders), 1999 (Offsite-box 171, Folder 6-7)
    - NGWSD, 1999 (Offsite-box 171, Folder 8)
    - Summit (2 folders), 2001 (Offsite-box 171, Folder 9-10)
    - Women's Global Challenge (2 folders), 2001 (Offsite-box 171, Folder 11-12)
    - NGWSD, 1999 (Offsite-box 171, Folder 13)
    - BJK candle party (12 folders), 2003 (Offsite-box 171, Folder 14-25)
    - BJK/ Diane Stone correspondence (14 folders), 2001-2002 (Offsite-box 172, Folder 1-14)
    - Donor files, alphabetical We-Ya (70 folders), circa 1999-2001 (Offsite-box 172, Folder 15-84)
    - Donor files, alphabetical Ya-Z (23 folders), circa 1999-2001 (Offsite-box 173, Folder 1-23)
    - Donor files, deceased (6 folders), circa 1999-2001 (Offsite-box 173, Folder 24-29)
    - BJK tribute messages, 2003 (Offsite-box 173, Folder 30)
    - Annual report non-NYAD donations, 2003 (Offsite-box 173, Folder 31)
    - Golf outing playbook [disassembled binder] (3 folders), 1999-2000 (Offsite-box 173, Folder 32-34)
    - Team with WSF [disassembled binder] (2 folders), 1999 (Offsite-box 173, Folder 35-36)
    - Ad hoc committee Dinner revenue potential [disassembled binder] (3 folders), 2002 (Offsite-box 173, Folder 37-39)
    - NYAD volunteer playbook [disassembled binder] (3 folders), 2006 (Offsite-box 174, Folder 1-3)
    - GoGirlGo Atlanta [disassembled binder] (2 folders), 2008 (Offsite-box 174, Folder 4-5)
    - Hall of Fame induction [disassembled binder] (2 folders), 2008 (Offsite-box 174, Folder 6-7)
    - GoGirlGo challenge marathon playbook [disassembled binder], 2008 (Offsite-box 174, Folder 8)
    - NYAD [disassembled binder], 2011 (Offsite-box 174, Folder 9)
    - NYAD [disassembled binder], 2012 (Offsite-box 174, Folder 10)
    - NYAD [disassembled binder], 2011 (Offsite-box 174, Folder 11)
    - The Billies Playbook [disassembled binder] (5 folders), 2006 (Offsite-box 174, Folder 12-16)
    - Grassroots events research [disassembled binder] (1 of 3 folders), 2001-2002 (Offsite-box 174, Folder 17)
    - Grassroots events research [disassembled binder] (2 of 3 folders), 2001-2002 (Offsite-box 175, Folder 1-2)
    - The Billies [disassembled binder] (4 folders), 2006 (Offsite-box 175, Folder 3-6)
    - Development office samples: mailings and events [disassembled binder] (3 folders), 2003 (Offsite-box 175, Folder 7-9)
    - Nancy Hogshead-Makar tributes [disassembled binder] (2 folders), 2004 (Offsite-box 175, Folder 10-11)
    - The Billies [disassembled binder] (2 folders), 2008 (Offsite-box 175, Folder 12-13)
    - The Billies [disassembled binder], 2010 (Offsite-box 175, Folder 14)
    - Annual Salute sales [disassembled binder] (1 of 4 folders), 2010 (Offsite-box 175, Folder 15)
    - Annual Salute sales [disassembled binder] (3 of 4 folders), 2010 (Offsite-box 176, Folder 1-3)
    - Annual fund [disassembled binder], 1998-2002 (Offsite-box 176, Folder 4)
    - Development samples: mailings/ events [disassembled binder] (2 folders), 2004 (Offsite-box 176, Folder 5-6)
    - Shipping [disassembled binder], 2005-2007 (Offsite-box 176, Folder 7)
    - Development mailings catalog [disassembled binder] (2 folders), 2008 (Offsite-box 176, Folder 8-9)
    - 31st Annual Salute to Women in Sports [disassembled binder] (2 folders), 2010 (Offsite-box 176, Folder 10-11)
    - 30th Annual Salute to Women in Sports master account bill [disassembled binder], 2009 (Offsite-box 176, Folder 14)
    - Special appeals and informational mailing [disassembled binder] (2 folders), 1999-2002 (Offsite-box 177, Folder 1-2)
    - Billies bill [disassembled binder], 2007 (Offsite-box 177, Folder 3)
    - WSF conference [disassembled binder] (2 folders), 2008 (Offsite-box 177, Folder 4-5)
    - NYAD [disassembled binder] (2 folders), 2008-2010 (Offsite-box 177, Folder 6-7)
    - NYAD sales [disassembled binder] (4 folders), 2009 (Offsite-box 177, Folder 8-11)
    - 32nd Annual Salute to Women in Sports mailing (2 folders), 2011 (Offsite-box 177, Folder 12-13)
    - 32nd Annual Salute to Women in Sports program (2 folders), 2011 (Offsite-box 178, Folder 1-2)
    - 33rd Annual Salute to Women in Sports program (2 folders), 2012 (Offsite-box 178, Folder 3-4)
    - 33rd Annual Salute to Women in Sports silent auction booklet (3 folders), 2012 (Offsite-box 178, Folder 5-7)
    - 34th Annual Salute to Women in Sports invitations (4 folders), 2013 (Offsite-box 178, Folder 8-11)
    - 34th Annual Salute to Women in Sports silent auction booklet (2 folders), 2013 (Offsite-box 178, Folder 12-13)
    - 35th Annual Salute to Women in Sports invitations (2 of 4 folders), 2014 (Offsite-box 178, Folder 14-15)
    - 35th Annual Salute to Women in Sports invitations (2 of 4 folders), 2014 (Offsite-box 179, Folder 1-2)
    - 27th Annual Salute to Women in Sports invitations, 2006 (Offsite-box 179, Folder 3)
    - 28th Annual Salute to Women in Sports invitations, 2007 (Offsite-box 179, Folder 4)
    - 28th Annual Salute to Women in Sports program, 2007 (Offsite-box 179, Folder 5)
    - 29th Annual Salute to Women in Sports invitations, 2008 (Offsite-box 179, Folder 6)
    - The Billies invitations, 2006 (Offsite-box 179, Folder 7)
    - The Billies program (2 folders), 2006 (Offsite-box 179, Folder 8-9)
    - The Billies invitations, 2007 (Offsite-box 179, Folder 10)
    - The Billies invitations, 2008 (Offsite-box 179, Folder 11)
    - WSF holiday card, circa 2005-2010 (Offsite-box 179, Folder 12)
    - So the World May Hear awards gala invitation, 2013 (Offsite-box 179, Folder 13)
    - Mail returned to WSF (4 of 5 folders), 2011-2013 (Offsite-box 179, Folder 14-17)
    - Mail returned to WSF (1 of 5 folders), 2011-2013 (Offsite-box 180, Folder 1)
    - Annual Salute to Women in Sports program, 2004 (Offsite-box 180, Folder 2)
    - Annual Salute to Women in Sports program, 2005 (Offsite-box 180, Folder 3)
    - Annual Salute to Women in Sports auction booklet, 2005 (Offsite-box 180, Folder 4)
    - 27th Annual Salute to Women in Sports program, 2006 (Offsite-box 180, Folder 5)
    - Annual Salute to Women in Sports program, 2007 (Offsite-box 180, Folder 6)
    - 29th Annual Salute to Women in Sports mailing and program, 2008 (Offsite-box 180, Folder 7)
    - 30th Annual Salute to Women in Sports program, 2009 (Offsite-box 180, Folder 8)
    - 33rd Annual Salute to Women in Sports invitations (5 folders), 2012 (Offsite-box 180, Folder 9-13)
    - 32nd Annual Salute to Women in Sports silent auction booklet, 2011 (Offsite-box 181, Folder 1)
    - 34th Annual Salute to Women in Sports program (3 folders), 2013 (Offsite-box 181, Folder 2-4)
    - 34th Annual Salute to Women in Sports silent auction booklet (2 folders), 2013 (Offsite-box 181, Folder 5-6)
    - Annual Salute to Women in Sports athlete face book, 2012 (Offsite-box 181, Folder 7)
    - Development mailings (2 folders), 2011-2012 (Offsite-box 181, Folder 8-9)
    - USA Today Billie Awards clipping, 2006 (Offsite-box 181, Folder 10)
    - NGWSD collaboration agreement, 1997 (Offsite-box 218, Folder 10)
    - NGWSD CEO meeting, 1999 (Offsite-box 218, Folder 11)
    - NGWSD logo, 2000 (Offsite-box 218, Folder 12)
    - NGWSD strategic plan, 2002 (Offsite-box 218, Folder 13)
    - NGWSD NWLC, 2002-2003 (Offsite-box 218, Folder 14)
    - NGWSD, 2004 (Offsite-box 218, Folder 15)
    - NGWSD planning, 2005 (Offsite-box 218, Folder 16)
    - NGWSD, 2005 (Offsite-box 218, Folder 17)
    - NGWSD DC, 2005 (Offsite-box 218, Folder 18)
    - Annual Salute to Women in Sports programs, 1980-2018 (Offsite-box 219, Folder 15)
      Contains programs for the Annual Salute to Women in Sports, years 1980, 1989, 1999, 2009, and 2018.
    - Annual report, 1994 (Offsite-box 219, Folder 16)
    - Women's Sports Foundation employee/ intern handbook [binder], 1998 (Offsite-box 264, Item 1)
    - Sneaker Day [binder], 2003 May 16 (Offsite-box 264, Item 2)
    - GoGirlGo News playbook [binder], 2008 (Offsite-box 264, Item 3)
    - Insider Issues [binder], 1992-1997 (Offsite-box 264, Item 4)
    - Summit [binder], 1999 (Offsite-box 264, Item 6)
    - WSF Banners playbook [binder], 2000 (Offsite-box 264, Item 7)
    - Summit [binder], 2000 (Offsite-box 264, Item 8)
    - Summit [binder], 2001 (Offsite-box 264, Item 9)
    - Women's Sports Experience playbook [binder], 2006 (Offsite-box 265, Item 1)
    - Resolutions [binder], 2006 (Offsite-box 265, Item 2)
    - Early Foundation newsletters [binder], 1976-1984 (Offsite-box 265, Item 3)
    - Headway (newsletter before Women's Sports Experience) [binder], 1985-1991 (Offsite-box 265, Item 4)
    - Women's Sports Experience [binder], 1992-1997 (Offsite-box 265, Item 5)
    - Women's Sports Experience [binder], 1998-2004 (Offsite-box 265, Item 6)
    - Women's Sports Experience [binder], 2005-2008 (Offsite-box 266, Item 1)
    - Sportstalk and GoGoGirl News [binder], 1994-2008 (Offsite-box 266, Item 2)
    - Publications samples [binder], 1986-1998 (Offsite-box 266, Item 3)
    - Events publications [binder], 1994-2000 (Offsite-box 266, Item 4)
    - Stationary/ Image System playbook [binder], circa 1995-2000 (Offsite-box 266, Item 5)
    - Gatorade [binder], 2002 (Offsite-box 266, Item 6)
  - Subseries IV.F. Community impact records, 1983-2008; 15 Linear feet in 15 record cartons
    Subseries IV.F contains records pertaining to the Community Impact functions of WSF, including grant-making programs, student athlete programs, and professional athlete programs. Particular programs and services documented include the Coaches Advisory Roundtable (often shortened to CAR), athlete Travel and Training Grants, GoGirlGo grants, the Athlete Ambassador Program, the Athlete's Speaker Service, and various awards granted by WSF. Record types include grantee applications and winner records, correspondence, budget forms, publicity materials, and program guides, called "playbooks," for staff. This subseries also contains an alphabetical run of subject files for athletes and coaches considered for and inducted into the International Women's Hall of Fame. Records date from 1983-2008.
    - CAR information, 1991-1992 (Offsite-box 181, Folder 11)
    - CAR internship application, 1991 (Offsite-box 181, Folder 12)
    - CAR budget rent-a-car sponsorship, 1991 (Offsite-box 181, Folder 13)
    - CAR steering committee meetings, 1991 (Offsite-box 181, Folder 14)
    - CAR code of ethics statements of purpose, 1991 (Offsite-box 181, Folder 15)
    - CAR fact sheet, circa 1991 (Offsite-box 181, Folder 16)
    - Organizations - fact sheet file, circa 1990 (Offsite-box 181, Folder 17)
    - Amateur Athletic Union, 1986 (Offsite-box 181, Folder 18)
    - American Coaching Effectiveness Program (ACEP), 1987 (Offsite-box 181, Folder 19)
    - Amateur Softball Association, 1988 (Offsite-box 181, Folder 20)
    - American Volleyball Coaches Association, 1991 (Offsite-box 181, Folder 21)
    - College Field Hockey Association, 1986 (Offsite-box 181, Folder 22)
    - Collegiate Council of Women Athletic Administrators, 1988 (Offsite-box 181, Folder 23)
    - Ladies Professional Golf Association, 1987 (Offsite-box 181, Folder 24)
    - National Association for Girls and Women in Sport, 1987 (Offsite-box 181, Folder 25)
    - National Association of Intercollegiate Athletes, 1988 (Offsite-box 181, Folder 26)
    - National Collegiate Athletic Association, 1989 (Offsite-box 181, Folder 27)
    - National Federation of State High School Associations, 1991 (Offsite-box 181, Folder 28)
    - National Junior College Athletic Associations, 1988 (Offsite-box 181, Folder 29)
    - National Soccer Coaches Association of America, 1991 (Offsite-box 181, Folder 30)
    - National Coaches Softball Association, 1986 (Offsite-box 181, Folder 31)
    - National Youth Sport Coaches Association, 1989 (Offsite-box 181, Folder 32)
    - The Athletics Congress, 1989 (Offsite-box 181, Folder 33)
    - United States Youth Soccer Association, circa 1988-1989 (Offsite-box 181, Folder 34)
    - Women's Basketball Coaches Association, 1989 (Offsite-box 181, Folder 35)
    - Terri Laswell, 1987 (Offsite-box 181, Folder 36)
    - Acosta & Carpenter, 1988 (Offsite-box 181, Folder 37)
    - Advocacy, 1988 (Offsite-box 181, Folder 38)
    - CAR operating code, 1988 (Offsite-box 181, Folder 39)
    - CAR at-large members, 1991 (Offsite-box 181, Folder 40)
    - CAR membership survey form, 1990 (Offsite-box 181, Folder 41)
    - CAR membership committee, 1990-1991 (Offsite-box 181, Folder 42)
    - CAR sponsorship proposal, circa 1990 (Offsite-box 181, Folder 43)
    - CAR operating code, 1990 (Offsite-box 181, Folder 44)
    - General correspondence, 1989 (Offsite-box 181, Folder 45)
    - Correspondence and labels, 1990 (Offsite-box 181, Folder 46)
    - CAR correspondence in, 1990 (Offsite-box 182, Folder 1)
    - CAR correspondence out, 1990 (Offsite-box 182, Folder 2)
    - CAR meeting, 1988 (Offsite-box 182, Folder 3)
    - CAR annual meeting, 1989 (Offsite-box 182, Folder 4)
    - CAR minutes, 1990 (Offsite-box 182, Folder 5)
    - Annual conference CAR meeting, 1991 (Offsite-box 182, Folder 6)
    - CAR annual meeting, 1992 (Offsite-box 182, Folder 7)
    - CAR budget/ expenses, 1991 (Offsite-box 182, Folder 8)
    - CAR budget/ expenses, 1990 (Offsite-box 182, Folder 9)
    - CAR budget and expenses, 1989 (Offsite-box 182, Folder 10)